Aleksandr Krivonosov

Objective: C++ software developer

Primary Skills:

- C++
- Java
- JavaScript
- SQL
- R
- C#

Professional Highlights

Information Technology professional in software development including servers, multithreading programs, network games, add-ins for CAD systems. Also have experience in 3D graphics, driver development, construction of mathematical models of complex systems, creating simple sites, predicting data using neural networks. Interested in predicting data, bigDATA, driver development. Excellent work in team. Leadership qualities.

Work experience

WILDEC 06/2016 – 02/2018

C++ Developer

AMCbridge 03/2018 – now

C++ Developer

Education

DNU named after Oles' Honchar

2013 - 2018

Master's degree in Applied Mathematics, educational program: computer modeling and computational methods.

Personal features and information

English level: upper-intermediate.

Contacts:

email: sahlet.official@gmail.com

skype: sahlet